(Penny:)It does have
a camera in it.
(Leonard:)Baby's listening.
(knocks)
SHELDON: Leonard?
(knocks) Leonard?
(Raj:)What?
(Sheldon:)I spoke to the reporter
at the magazine.
(Bernadette:)What happened?
Did you tell him it was my idea?
(Amy:)I did.
(Leonard:)Thank you. What did he say?
(Sheldon:)He said they made
the editorial decision
(Sheldon:)to only cite the lead scientist.
(Leonard:)Why did he think
you're the lead scientist?
It was my idea!
(Raj:)You know,
for an extra four bucks,
(Penny:)I can have this thing
here tomorrow.
(Sheldon:)Well, I know it
was your idea,
(Sheldon:)but the reporter said he's been
following my work for a while,
(Sheldon:)and the only reason they even
mentioned it in the magazine
(Sheldon:)is 'cause my name is on it.
(Penny:)You know what? I did it.
What's four bucks?
(Leonard:)If you're trying
to make me feel better,
(Leonard:)it's not working.
(Sheldon:)Well... then what if I told you
(Sheldon:)that I added your name
to the cable bill?
(Sheldon:)No.
Oh.